# **VISHAL JANI**

## **Business Development Manager**

Address Ahmedabad, GJ, 380013

Phone 997 480 6611

E-mail vishaljani80@gmail.com

Talented, sales-driven, recognised expert in the fields of direct sales and sales management. Equipped with 4+ years of experience in the areas of sales, marketing, business operations and development. Eager to advance my career and obtain a sales director position within a reputable, growth-oriented company.

#### **Skills**

- Leadership
- Lead Generation
- Sales
- Process optimization
- Communication
- Team Handling
- Team Training

# **Work Experience**

Name of the company: The P4, Ahmedabad, Gujarat

Duration: September 2022 to Current

Designation: Business Development Manager

Profile: **B2B sales with school** 

- Prospected for potential new clients and turned them into increased avenues of business.
- Developed and oversaw marketing functions to identify key marketing strategies for successful new customer acquisition and sales growth.
- Developed contacts with the Schools.
- Prospecting Schools for collaboration with our Organization.
- Conduct meetings with Principals, coordinators and school admin for product demo and explaining to them the need of the platform.
- Signing MoU with schools & Institutes to provide our service offerings.

Name of the company: Summachar Pathshala, Ahmedabad, Gujarat

Duration: August 2021 to August 2022

Designation: Business Development Manager

Profile: **B2B sales with school** 

- Prospected for potential new clients and turned them into increased avenues of business.
- Developed and oversaw marketing functions to identify key marketing strategies for successful new customer acquisition and sales growth.
- Developed contacts with the potential customers.(school & coaching institutes)
- Prospecting Schools for collaboration with our Organization.
- Conduct meetings with Principals, coordinators and school admin for product demo and explaining to them the need of the platform.
- Conduct campaigns, webinars, seminars in campus and institutions.
- Visiting various institutions for tie ups with universities.
- Signing MoU with schools & Institutes to provide our service offerings.

Name of the company: THINK & LEARN PVT LTD, AHMEDABAD, GUJARAT

Duration: January 2021 to July 2021

Designation : Business Development Training Manager

Profile: OJT sales Training to new employees for B2C sales

- Identify training needs according to needs
- Based on research, plan and implement training programs that will prepare employees for the next step of their career paths
- Lead, teach, onboard and evaluate new trainers
- Present all the technical and supply training requirements
- Prepare budget for training programs and workshops
- Encourage employees for training performance
- Track employee success and progress
- Communicate all the training programs on a timely basis
- Average batch size is 17- 20 Associates.
- The role is a mixture of sales and training.

Name of the company: THINK & LEARN PVT LTD, AHMEDABAD, GUJARAT

Duration: December 2018 to December 2020

**Designation: Senior Business Development Associate** 

Profile: **B2C** sales

- This is an individual contributor role in an employee-oriented, high
- performance Education environment that emphasizes on spreading the unique way of learning.
- The role will start with contacting potential customers (parents and
- students) to set up meetings, counsel the students on learning pedagogies.
- Taking up revenue responsibility.

# **Education**

Sr. No	Qualification	Name of the College/School	Name of the Board/University	Year Of Passing	Percentage Obtained
1.	Master of Business Administration	Indian school of Business Management	Indian school of Business Management	2018	70%
2.	Bachelor of Business Administration	B.k.Majumdar institute of Business administration	Ahmedabad University	2016	68%
3.	Higher secondary certificate	Swastik school	Gujarat Board	2013	76%
4.	Secondary school certificate	Swastik school	Gujarat Board	2011	81%

### **Personal Information**

Date of Birth : 04/01/1996 Marital status : Married